<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docker on interesting things</title>
    <link>https://hairyhenderson.github.io/blog/public/categories/docker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docker on interesting things</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 20:10:02 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hairyhenderson.github.io/blog/public/categories/docker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Whipping tablecloths with Docker for AWS, CloudFormation, and Terraform</title>
      <link>https://hairyhenderson.github.io/blog/public/post/migrating-d4aws-to-novpc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 20:10:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairyhenderson.github.io/blog/public/post/migrating-d4aws-to-novpc/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Docker for AWS (D4AWS) ever since I was accepted into the public beta, and have been running it in production for a while. One of the best features of D4AWS is that you can deploy it without needing any client-side tooling, due to its use of AWS CloudFormation (CFN).
This simplicity can also be a problem, since CloudFormation can be quite inflexible. In the early days, if you wanted to add a D4AWS stack to an existing VPC, for example, you were out of luck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About gomplate</title>
      <link>https://hairyhenderson.github.io/blog/public/post/about_gomplate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 23:14:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairyhenderson.github.io/blog/public/post/about_gomplate/</guid>
      <description>I released gomplate version 1.6.0 (here) a couple weeks ago. It was a fairly big release, as these things go, but I realized that I haven&amp;rsquo;t ever really introduced gomplate formally. So this post is an attempt to describe what it is, why I thought it needed to exist, and what&amp;rsquo;s happened with it over the last year and a half.
And now, some history&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of Docker, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been using it for a few years, and trying to wrap most programs I use as Docker images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting YubiKey working with Docker Content Trust on OS X</title>
      <link>https://hairyhenderson.github.io/blog/public/post/yubikey-dct/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2016 22:19:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hairyhenderson.github.io/blog/public/post/yubikey-dct/</guid>
      <description>Getting YubiKey working with Docker Content Trust on OS X This wasn&amp;rsquo;t as straightforward as I would&amp;rsquo;ve liked, so I&amp;rsquo;m documenting this here.
First, some super-useful sources:
 Diogo Mónica&amp;rsquo;s blog posting from DockerCon EU 2015 (DOCKER CONTENT TRUST GETS HARDWARE SIGNING) docker/notary#779 (Improve docs for typical CI usage with docker+notary) The YubiKey PIV CLI tool v1.4.3 zip docker/toolbox#461 (from here I gleaned that /usr/local/docker/lib is understood by notary)  I only figured this out because the folks above did most of the work!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>